<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Learn Forever</string>
    <string name="title_activity_navigation_drawer">NavigationDrawerActivity</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <!--Navigation Drawer-->
    <string name="navigation_drawer_menu_item_home">Home</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_menu_item_categories">Categories</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_menu_item_revise">Revise</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_menu_item_settings">Settings</string>

    <!--Help strings-->
    <string name="help_string_note_activity">This is the create/view note activity.\n\nUse this screen to add a new note or edit an existing note.\n\nUse the switch button to learn this note.Turning this on will set reminders on preset intervals.These frequent revise intervals help you to learn something forever.\n\nYou can also change this interval setting from the settings page. \n\nFunctions:\n\nWhile creating a note:\n\n
1. Tap on the mic button on the top right corner to dictate your note\n
2. Tap on show all views to show all the views (title, content in short, category, content)\n
3. Tap on the change interval button to change the intervals you want the note to be reminded on.\n\n
        While viewing a note:\n\n
        1. Tap on the volume button to start reading the note.\n
        2. Tap on the delete button to delete the note.\n
        3. Tap on show all views to show all the views (title, content in short, category, content)\n
        4. Tap on Upcoming revise dates to show all the upcoming reminder dates in MM/DD/YY \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="help_string_home">This is the home screen, here you will find all the notes that you create.\n\n
Use this place to see, edit and delete the notes. \n\n
Use the plus button given in the bottom right corner to create a new note. \n\n
Functions:\n\n
1. Use the delete button to delete the note.\n
2. Use the volume button to read out notes. \n
3. Use the search button to open search.\n
4. Use the send note to send notes to other applications.\n
5. Use the revise button to revise the selected notes.\n
6. Use the sort notes to sort notes in different order.\n
7. Use the settings button to open settings.\n
8. Use the cancel button to cancel selection mode.\n\n

Please note:\n
In order to use these functions either first click on the icons to activate selection mode or long press on the notes.
Now just select all the notes you want the action to be performed. Then just click on the action to complete the action.\n\n
</string>
    <string name="help_string_categories">This section shows a list of categories. \n\n Press on a category to see the notes only for that category. \n\n Long click on an item to start revising all the notes of that category.\n</string>
    <string name="help_string_revise">This section shows the notes that are due to be revised by you. \n\n All the notes that are not revised since you revised are shown in this section.\n\n Please select any note to start revising.</string>
    <string name="help_string_settings">This app allows for the following settings to be changed \n\n 1. Revise Intervals - Click this to change the frequency with which you wnt the notes to be revised. \n\n 2. New Note settings - Click this setting to change the sections you want to see while creating a new note. \n\n 3. Notification time - Click on this setting to change the time you want to be notified to revise notes.
        \n\n 4. Reading speed - Click on this settings to change the rate of speech for the whole app. \n\n 5. Layout style - Click on this setting to change how the notes are presented in the home fragment \n\n 6. Click on the give feedback setting to give feedback.\n\n 7. Log out - Click this setting to log out and clear all data from this device.\n\n </string>
    <string name="about_us">
PRIVACY POLICY &amp; ABOUT DISCLAIMER \n\n
Privacy Policy\n\n
Saumy Kukreti built the Forever app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by Saumy Kukreti at no cost and is intended for use as is.\n\n
This page is used to inform website visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.\n\n
If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that I collect is used for providing and improving the Service. I will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.\n\n
The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at Learn Forever unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.\n\n
Information Collection and Use\n\n
For a better experience, while using our Service, I may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information. The information that I request is retained on your device and firebase(Google) servers and is not collected by me in any way.\n\n
The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.\n\n
Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app\n\n
1. Google Play Services (https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)\n
2. Firebase Analytics (https://firebase.google.com/policies/analytics/)\n\n
Log Data\n\n
I want to inform you that whenever you use my Service, in a case of an error in the app I collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing my Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.\n\n
Cookies\n\n
Cookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your device internal memory.\n\n
This Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly. However, the app may use third party code and libraries that use “cookies” to collection information and to improve their services. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of this Service.\n\n
Service Providers\n\n
I may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:\n\n
To facilitate our Service;\n\n
To provide the Service on our behalf;\n\n
To perform Service-related services; or\n\n
To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.\n\n
I want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.\n\n
Security\n\n
I value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and I cannot guarantee its absolute security.\n\n
Links to Other Sites\n\n
This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by me. Therefore, I strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. I have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.\n\n
Children’s Privacy\n\n
These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. I do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. In the case I discover that a child under 13 has provided me with personal information, I immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact me so that I will be able to do necessary actions.\n\n
Changes to This Privacy Policy\n\n
I may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. I will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.\n\n
Contact Us\n\n
If you have any questions or suggestions about my Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact me.\n\n
This privacy policy page was created at privacypolicytemplate.net and modified/generated by App Privacy Policy Generator\n\n
        About the application\n\n
        This application is designed with the sole purpose of learning new things easier. \n\nBy constantly revising a particular note in certain intervals, we transfer the memory from short term memory to long term memory. \n\nThis app also has Text to speech integrated into it. According to us, the more are the source of inputs while we are learning, the better we learn. \n\n</string>

</resources>
